知らないの？ 普通の人間とは全く違う
Hello? Pitou-sama? This is Komugi.
生命エネルギーに溢れた 人間がいるって話。
I'm fine, so don't worry.
「レアもの」？
Got it...
どんなカラクリだ？ 急に強くなった感じがするぞ
Now, Pitou is also under my spell...
「ナルカミ」！
The spell of the lie that will
free Pitou from that curse.
最初は　グ
You listened to my request.
ジャン！　ケン！ グ!!
So I will be honest with you.
一人前になりたいなら ここは格好の修羅場。
He is already
ただし　まともな神経じゃ 一歩も耐えられん。
dead.
あぁ　分かってる。 あのキメラアントは 完全に気配を消していたしな。
Anger x And x Light
うん。
The tables have been turned.
あっ…。 あっ…。
The way things are looking,
that Gon boy will be killed.
行くぞ。
I am the only one who can stop Pitou.
そう　ここがＮＧＬの裏の顔だ。
Get lost, scumbag!
麻薬工場。 その通り。
Leave her to me.
今　ちまたで 流行している飲むドラッグ
I swear upon these eyes that
I will not let them have her.
ディーディーの製造工場。
Yeah, I'm counting on you.
近くに原料のビラ畑もあるはずだ。
Speed of Lightning!
自然保護区とは笑わせるぜ。
Gon...
麻薬だけじゃないぜ。
Wait for me to get there!
半径　何ｍぐらい探れんの？
Gon...
４５ｍほどだ。 よっ…　４５ｍ!? 体調と精神状態で ２３ｍ増減するがな。
I'm sorry to say this, but I must kill you.
来るぞ。
For the King.
あっ…　うぅ。
kill me? You aren't going to heal him?
クウン　クウン…。 お前ら　うるせぇぞ！
Then you really aren't
あ？
going to heal Kite...
てめぇは　犬だろうが！ あ…。
Liar.
決めたぞ。
What is this?
悪党と交じることで
I don't care
えっ　交じるって？ 摂食交配だろ？
if this is the end...
ホ！
I'll use everything.
ホッホ！　さぁ　食らいなされ
I was right.
防御不可能の千手拳！
His power is now equal
ハ！
to that of the King!
んっ!? ハァ…!! フッギャ!!
I'll kill you, Pitou!
やっぱり　こいつら すごく硬い！ 昆虫の頑強さと 人間の柔軟さ…
Terpsichora!
ん？　何を考えていなさる？
Exceed your limits, and dance!
最初は　グ！ なっ！
I must stop him here!
「コロ」に決定！ 久々にスイッチ入れるか
It can't be!
ヤァ！
Is he heading for the King?
蚊　蚊　蚊！　おバカさん こっちが本命の毒針よ。 うっ…。
Come.
どう？　神経毒が 全身に広がって行く感触は。
I don't want to destroy this place.
あとは　ヤク漬けにすれば 人間犬の出来上がり。 そっちは終わった？
This way.
あら　まだなの？
Follow me.
ハァ　ハァ…　うぅ…。
I don't know how he did it, but he's forced his body to mature to a point
うぅ！ ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…！
at which he's able to defeat me.
右腕８本で奴を押さえ込み かみつき　毒を送り込む
First comes
)
rock...
ふざけんな！　てめぇに 選択権なんざ　ねえんだよ。
Rock.
さぁ　俺を楽しませろ。
王が自分の城にいるのは 当然だろう。 ここには　異臭を放つ薬品も多い。
Sinking deeply into unconsciousness, Pitou felt a sense of relief.
お前らが好む場所とは思えんが。
Thank goodness...
ＮＧＬのボスは　どうした？ ここにいたはずだ。
This power could only be achieved through
the sacrifice of his own life energy.
とっくに女王様の腹の中に おさまってんじゃねえか？
He's prepared to never use Nen again.
フハハ…！ ここから俺の世界を築く。 全世界を牛耳ってやる。
That was the resolve required
to perform this feat.
低俗な　やからには。 ハハッ　そうかよ！
An enemy blessed with immense talent
早いとこ てめぇを全裸に　ひんむいて 首輪をはめてやるぜ！
has been forced to exchange all
of that talent for this power.
う！
that he will kill...
なっ…！ この！　下りやがれ！
Having used Speed of Lightning to race
to Gon, Killua arrived to hear...
トゥルルルル…！ ナメやがって。 犬にするのは　やめだ 殺してやる！
Which one of them is doing that?
４か　ハズレだな。
Gon!
何を!? この俺様に　ハズレなんか ねえんだよ　この野郎！
And what he found was...
奴が打って来たパンチをガード 同時に押さえつけて　かみつく
...for the final, shattering blow.
チ!! なぬ！
Kite...
つ　剣!?
I finished the job, the way you taught me to.
あり得ん！　一体　どこに 隠し持っていたというのだ？
So...
しかし　好都合かもしれぬ！ このまま　やられたフリをして
Gon, is that you?
ア！
But he realized the difference at once.
胴体を切ったくらいで 安心するな。 頭と胴体が切り離されても 一日くらいなら
Bisky's appearance changed, but there wasn't a massive increase
in the aura contained within her. And in Bisky's case, But Gon's done the opposite!
生きていられるような 生命力を持つ連中。
How many years?
確実に　頭を潰せ。
More than ten? Decades?
そして　欲を言えば　やる時は できるだけ素早く　静かにな ハハハ…！
This would have been the result
of years of endless training.
あっ　あの時の！ 俺達を撃った奴だ！ 口の中にルーレット！
What price did he have to pay
to obtain so much aura?
ユンジュは 工場をねぐらにしていたな。
Pitou's devotion to the King was so great
ということは　レアものは まだ工場付近にいますね。 行くぜ　今夜はごちそうだ！ ごちそうだ！
that even after death, Terpsichora clad
itself in even more powerful Nen, transforming Pitou into a corpse puppet
ready to leap forward in pursuit of its prey, its sole purpose to kill Gon.
使い勝手が良さそうだ。 そりゃ　まぁ さっきのに比べればね。 うん。 ゴンは　どうやら 強化　変化　放出の能力を
In that fraction of a second,
shorter than the blink of an eye, Killua heard Gon speak.
ジャンケンに見立てて 使っているようだな。
It's okay.
うん　俺自身の得意な「念」の系統は 強化系だけど。
It doesn't hurt. I'm not trying to be tough.
キルアは電気…　変化系か？ ああ　まだまだ威力はないし すぐ空になるけどね。
I'm kind of happy...
嫌でもレベルアップするさ 急ぐぞ
I finally get to be the same
巣は近い。
as Kite was then.
ハァ　ハァ…　ヘヘヘ！
You can have my right arm.
全身からエネルギーが 溢れ出て来るぜ！
First comes rock...
何なんだよ　こりゃ！　え！
Gon!
どうした？
It's time for you
部下からの信号だ ラモットの様子が変らしい。
to sleep, too.
ラモットが？
Stop... You can't!
フッフッフ…。
If you keep using this power, what will happen to you?
どうだい？　見てくれよ
Rock.
生まれ変わった気分だぜ！
Paper.
ダハハハ…！ 見えるか　ペギー　あの光が。
Gon!